Guide to the Walter Gardner Hall Papers, 1923-1990 MS 280
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: The Democratic Party, 1944-1976
  - Subseries A: Party Politics, (1944-1973)
    - WGH - Franklin Jones re Liberal Democrats and LBJ, Dec. 1963 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, Dec. 1963 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - Pritchard and Abbott, March 1963 - June 1964 (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - WGH - Bill Kilgarlin - Workers for the Democratic Party, Feb. 1964 (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - WGH - Tony Korioth - Kennedy Library, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - Poll tax lists - Voting eligibility, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - League of Women Voters - Poll tax, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - WGH - John F. Beck - CBS news and campaign fund raising, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - V.O.T.E. - Larry Goodwyn, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - Young Democrats of Texas, July 1964 (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - Texas Democratic Coalition, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - Congressional redistricting in Texas, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - Galveston Co. Convention, May 1964 (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - Texas Democratic Convention, Sept. 1964 (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - Texas Bill of Rights Foundation, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - News coverage - Democratic Party, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - WGH - Heap re Texas Right to Work Law, Jan. - Feb. 1965 (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - Ed Harris Appreciation Dinner, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 131)
    - Trip to Austin -, 1965 May 25, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - Widening Highway 3 from Houston to Galveston, June 1965 (Box 6, Folder 133)
    - Texas Observer, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 134)
    - Galveston Co. Democratic Party, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 135)
    - Political Assassination of Houston Chronicle editors, Sept. 1965 (Box 6, Folder 136)
    - Amendment One - letters seeking support, Oct. 1965 (Box 6, Folder 137)
    - Opposition to 4 yr. terms for governor and state reps. - Const. amendment, Oct. - Nov. 1965 (Box 6, Folder 138)
    - Poll tax, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 139)
    - Repeal of 14 (b) Taft - Hartley Act, June 1965 (Box 6, Folder 140)
    - Houston Manned Spacecraft Center, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 141)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 142)
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 143)
    - Pritchard and Abbott, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 144)
    - WGH - Clark Thompson - Sam Low - Albert Thomas re customs service reorganization, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 145)
    - News coverage - Democratic Party, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - Dickinson politics, Jan. 1966 (Box 6, Folder 147)
    - Campaign of Bill Kilgarlin for Bob Casey's congressional seat, Jan. 1966 (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - Preparations for 1970 census, May 1966 (Box 6, Folder 149)
    - Chocolate Bayou Navigation Project, June - July 1966 (Box 6, Folder 150)
    - Funding of scientific research, Aug. 1966 (Box 6, Folder 151)
    - Houston Manned Spacecraft Center - Jim Maloney, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 152)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - Galveston Co. Democratic Conventions, May 1966 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Washington trip - June 20-22, 1966, June 1966 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - WGH - Tom Caldwell re making voting easier, Oct. - Nov. 1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Texas Bill of Rights Foundation, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Texas Observer - Ronnie Dugger, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Tax reform in Texas - Charles E. McClure, Jr., Aug. - Dec. 1966 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Pritchard and Abbott, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - News coverage - Democratic Party, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Tax reform in Texas - Charles E. McClure, Jr., Jan. - April 1967 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Washington trip - Jan. 25-28, Jan. - Feb. 1967 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Texas AFL - CIO, March - Nov. 1967 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Washington trip - August, July - Aug. 1967 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - AFL - CIO voter participation, Sept. - Nov. 1967 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Texas Observer - Ronnie Dugger, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Vietnam, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Texas Bill of Rights Foundation, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Texas Liberal Democrats, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Congressional Quarterly re 1966 campaign contributions, Aug. 1967 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - WGH - Dean Neugent re Texas House Journal, Jan. 1967 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Branch Banking, Feb. 1967 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Redistricting in Texas, Feb. 1967 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Texas blue laws, Feb. 1967 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Texas H.B. 1021, March 1967 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Texas H.B. 1064, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Texas S.B. to create Galveston Bay Area Authority, April 1967 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Texas H.B. 879, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Marion Storm Memorial Fund, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Texas S.B. 539, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - WGH - J. Wiley Caldwell - state legislation, April 1967 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Texas City Chamber of Commerce Banquet, May 1967 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Texas Civil Liberties Union, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - WGH - Cecil J. Palmer re reforming state and federal government, July 1967 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Pritchard and Abbott, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - News coverage of the Democratic Party, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Texas AFL - CIO, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Texas Liberal Democrats Opinion Poll, Feb. 1968 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Washington trip - March 27-29, Jan. - March 1968 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - U.S. H.R. 15578, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Texas Bill of Rights Foundation, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Washington trip - May 8-9, May 1968 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Delegates and alternates to the Democratic National Convention, Aug. 1968 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Democratic National Convention - Chicago, July - Aug. 1968 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Democratic National Convention - Brief submitted to the Credentials Committee by the Loyal Democrats of Mississippi, Aug. 1968 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Democratic National Convention - Invitations received, Aug. 1968 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Re National Democratic Convention - Chicago, Sept. - Dec. 1968 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Clifton Carter - WGH re Alvin attorney, Nov. 1968 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - What's Right with LBJ - Texas Observer, Feb. - March 1968 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Texas Democratic Convention, June 11, 1968, May - June 1968 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Vietnam, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - U.S. Senate and Representative compaigns outside of Texas - Robert F. Kennedy, Edmund Muskie, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Bankers lobby, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Reaction in Africa to the death of M.L. King, April 1968 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Ads for Texas in N.Y. Times, March 1968 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Galveston Co. Democratic Party, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Texas Democratic Party - Preston Smith, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Texas Constitutional Amendment 4, Oct. 1968 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Marion Storm, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Pritchard and Abbott, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - News coverage of the Democratic Party, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Electoral College Reform Conference - Univ. of Houston, March - May 1969 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Texas' 61st Legislature, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Galveston Co. Democratic Party, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Galveston Co. road bonds, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Galveston Co. - Pritchard and Abbott, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Texas State Democratic Executive Committee, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - WGH - Stuart Long - Brazos River Authority, Feb. 1969 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Texas Observer - Ronnie Dugger, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Harris Co. voting statistics from Nov. 5, 1968, Jan. 1969 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Texas Library Systems Act, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Fred Hofheinz, J. Wiley Caldwell - San Jacinto Day Democratic Dinner, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Complaints about Pres. Nixon, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Democratic Reform Committee, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Texas Bill of Rights Foundation, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - WGH - J.R. Parten re Nixon, Vietnam and ABM, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Texans for Voter Registration, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Texas Civil Liberties Union, July 1969 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Gulf Coast Disposal Authority, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Redistricting of U.S. congressional districts in Texas, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Texas Today, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - WGH - Lillian Collier re comm. of 1000 to oppose Amendment 2, July 1969 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - WGH - William N. Kemp re John Connally's appointments, Jan. - Feb. 1969 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Texas Committee for Responsible Government - G. Godley, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - News coverage - Democratic Party, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Corporate taxes in Texas, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Unpaid political notes, Dec. 1970 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Vietnam, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Democratic Rebuilding Committee, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Texas State Democratic Executive Committee, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Voting studies, Oct. 1970 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - General election - Nov. 3, 1970 - Galveston Co. area (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Texas Today, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Campaign material for the general election, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Bankers political activity group, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Galveston Co. Democratic Party, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Galveston Co. Voting Precinct 38, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Galveston Co. Voting Precinct 39, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Galveston Co. Voting Precinct 40, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Galveston Co. Voting Precinct 41, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Dickinson Democratic headquarters, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Texas Bill of Rights Foundation, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Democratic Victory Dinner 10/1/70, Oct. 1970 (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - Texas Committee for Responsible Government - G. Godley, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - Pritchard and Abbott, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Galveston County Road Bond, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - History of politics in Texas since the New Deal - Barbara Day, Nov. 1970 - Jan. 1971 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - News coverage - Democratic Party, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Galveston Co. Democratic Party, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Tax relief for the elderly, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Gun control bills, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Jack Newfield, A Populist Manifesto: The Making of a New Majority, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Fagan Dickson, The Lesson of Vietnam, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Voter registration of students, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Bankers in politics, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - NASA, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Corporate income tax, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - U.S. Prayer Amendment, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Dinner for Ed Muskie, Dec. 1971 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Charles E. McLure Revenue Sharing: Alternative to Rational Fiscal Federalism, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Texas Observer - Ronnie Dugger, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Texas House of Representatives, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Tex. H.B. 339, March 1971 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - U.S. H.R. 7993 - Cooperative Extension Service, June 1971 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Texas Democratic Party, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Pritchard and Abbott - Galveston and Brazoria Co., 1971 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Federal Reserve interest rates, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Texas Bill of Rights Foundation, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - 1972 National Democratic Convention, Oct. 1971 - Sept. 1972 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - News coverage - Democratic Party, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Texas Observer - Ronnie Dugger, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Political contributions, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Galveston Co. Democratic Party, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Democratic National Committee - George McGovern, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Brazoria Co., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Labor and politics, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Taxes in Texas - Charles E. McLure, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Texas Association of Taxpayers, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Democratic primary runoff - June 3, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - General election - Nov. 1972 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Arthur H. Westing, Arms, Disarmament, and the Environment, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - 62nd Legislature - State of Texas, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Legislator - Banker Luncheon - 12/4/72, Nov. - Dec. 1972 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Re Decay in respect for Law - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, Nov. 1972 - April 1973 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - WGH - Roy R. Evans re WGH's appointment to the State Finance Commission, Feb. - March 1973 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Subseries B: Politicians, (1944-1976)
    - Wright Patman (speeches), 1944-1971 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Clark W. Thompson, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Senator Tom Connally, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Harold M. Tarpey, Commissioner 4 Galveston Co., 1945 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - WGH - Clark W. Thompson re Thompson running for the U.S. House and his position within the party, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - WGH - H. M. Tarpey, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - WGH - Clark Thompson, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Tom Connally, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - William O. Cooper, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Clark W. Thompson, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Jim Wright, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - James V. Allred, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Tom Connally, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - William O. Cooper, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Clark W. Thompson, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - James V. Allred, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Tom Connally, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - William O. Cooper, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Wright Patman, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Allan Shivers, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Clark Thompson, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Robert W. Calvert, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - William O. Cooper, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Allan Shivers, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - James V. Allred, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Tom Connally, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - William O. Cooper, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Bob Eckhardt, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Wright Patman, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Allan Shivers, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - John C. White, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Tom Connally, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Olin Culberson, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Oscar C. Dancy, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Jesse James, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - WGH - Sam LOW, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Wright Patman, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Allan Shivers, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Clark W. Thompson, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Jim Wright, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - William O. Cooper, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - Olin Culberson, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - William Kugle, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Jimmy Phillips, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Clark W. Thompson, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - William O. Cooper, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Clark Thompson, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Jimmy Phillips, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - A. R. Schwartz, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - James V. Allred, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Jesse James, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Clark W. Thompson, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Jim Wright, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - Lewis W. Cutrer, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - James Allred, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Olin Culberson, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Oscar Dancy, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Jimmy Phillips, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - J. Edwin Smith, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Clark W. Thompson, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Jim Wright, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Waggoner Carr, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - C. R. Johnson, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Jimmy Phillips, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - Clark W. Thompson, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Oscar Dancy, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Ray Holbrook, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - Maury Maverick, Jr., 1960 (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - Theodore R. Robinson, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - Clark W. Thompson, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - Jim Wright - Candidate for U.S. Senate, Nov. - Dec. 1960 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Don Yarborough, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - William O. Cooper, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - Bob Eckhardt, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Marshall Formby, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - Sam Low, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Wright Patman, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - Clark W. Thompson, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - Jim Wright - Senatorial campaign, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - Jim Wright - Possibility of Wright running for governor in 1962, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - Jim Wright - Appreciation dinner, Sept. 1961 (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - Jim Wright - WGH - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 125)
    - Don Brown, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 126)
    - William O. Cooper, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - Jim Wright, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Don Yarborough, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - John Connally - hope for a quick recovery, Nov. 1963 (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - William O. Cooper, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - C. R. Johnson - Pritchard and Abbott, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - J. Edwin Smith, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - Albert Thomas re a better feeling between Ralph and LBJ, Dec. 1963 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Clark W. Thompson, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - Jim Wright, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - Waggoner Carr, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 137)
    - John Connally re WGH unwillingness to serve in an appointed government position, Aug. 1964 (Box 8, Folder 138)
    - C. R. Johnson, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 139)
    - A. R. Schwartz - Appreciation dinner, March - April 1964 (Box 8, Folder 140)
    - J. Edwin Smith, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 141)
    - Clark W. Thompson, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 142)
    - Clark W. Thompson - Appreciation dinner, Nov. 1963 - Feb. 1964 (Box 8, Folder 143)
    - Jim Wright, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 144)
    - Chet Brooks, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 145)
    - Jack Brookshire, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 146)
    - Ed Clark, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 147)
    - William O. Cooper, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 148)
    - Paul B. Haring, Nov. 1965 (Box 8, Folder 149)
    - Sam Low, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 150)
    - A. R. (Babe) Schwartz, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 151)
    - Franklin Spears, Nov. 1965 (Box 8, Folder 152)
    - Adlai Stevenson, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 153)
    - Olin E. Teague, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 154)
    - Albert Thomas, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 155)
    - Clark W. Thompson, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 156)
    - Jim Wright - Senate race in 1966?, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 157)
    - Frank E. Vandiver - National Council on the Humanities, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 158)
    - G. W. (Heap) Alexander, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Jack Brooks - Clark W. Thompson - New 9th Congressional District, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Waggoner Carr - Race for U.S. Senate, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Ed Clark - re Texas politics, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - William O. Cooper - Politics and personal business, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Martin Dies, Jr., 1966 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Bob Eckhardt, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Ray Holbrook to Run for County Judge, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Ray Holbrook - Campaign for county judge, Jan. - July 1966 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Ray Holbrook - Poll lists used in campaign, May 1966 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Ray Holbrook - News coverage, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Ray Holbrook re Ralph Cagnola, 1966 - 1967 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - C. R. Johnson, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - A. R. (Babe) Schwartz, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Byron Skelton - Appreciation dinner, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Paul E. Stapp, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Olin E. Teague, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Clark W. Thompson, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Joe D. Waggoner, Jr., 1966 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - G. W. (Heap) Alexander, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Garth Bates, April 1967 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Jack Brooks, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Waggoner Carr, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Bob Casey, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - William O. Cooper - Politics and personal business, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - WGH - Fagan Dickson - Current politics - Vietnam, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Bob Eckhardt, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Ed Harris, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Ray Holbrook, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Hubert Humphrey, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - C. R. Johnson, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Barefoot Sanders, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - A. R. (Babe) Schwartz, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Olin E. Teague, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Jim Wright, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - G. W. (Heap) Alexander - Chicago Convention; gun control, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Ben Barnes, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Jack Brooks, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Waggoner Carr, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Bob Casey, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Ed Clark, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - William O. Cooper - Politics and personal business, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Fagan Dickson, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Bob Eckhardt, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Ray Holbrook, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Hubert H. Humphrey - Biographical material and public record, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Hubert H. Humphrey - Primary and nomination campaign - Correspondence, April - Aug. 1968 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Hubert H. Humphrey - Nomination campaign - Endorsements, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Hubert H. Humphrey - Nomination campaign - Literature, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Humphrey - Muskie campaign, Aug. - Sept. 1968 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Humphrey - Muskie campaign, Oct. 1968 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Humphrey - Muskie campaign, Nov. - Dec. 1968 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Humphrey - Muskie campaign material, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Humphrey - News coverage, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - C. R. Johnson, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Eugene McCarthy - Primary campaign, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Eugene McCarthy - Letters asking for WGH's support, July - Aug. 1968 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Crawford Martin, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Gus Mutscher, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Bernard Rapoport, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Tom Reavley, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Barefoot Sanders, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - A. R. (Babe) Schwartz, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Clark W. Thompson, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Jim Wright, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Don Yarborough, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Don Yarborough - News coverage, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - John Young, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Chet Brooks, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Jack Brooks, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Ed Clark, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - William O. Cooper, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Fagan Dickson, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Bob Eckhardt, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Hubert H. Humphrey, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Gus Mutscher, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Bernard Rapoport, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Barefoot Sanders, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - A. R. (Babe) Schwartz, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Preston Smith, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Will Wilson, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Lloyd Bentsen, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Jack Brooks, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 15)